Guide to the George P. Garrett Papers, 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
George P. Garrett papers 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
- Writings Series, 1957-1996 and undated
  - Writings by Others Subseries, ca. 1970-1994 and undated
    - Hummer, T. R., Poems
    - Humphries, Jefferson, On the Inevitability of Theory in Southern Literary
    - Hunter, Marsha, Poems
    - Ignotus, Miles, The Writer In A Hotwired Democracy
    - Jacobs, Lucky, Fragment. from dissertation
    - Juass, David, Glossolalia
    - Jacobson, Jane, Untitled story
    - Jacobson, Jane, The Well of the Seven Lambs
    - Janiszewski, Steven, Guacamole Tostada, (2 folders) (Box WO9)
    - Janiszewski, Steven, It's Only Natural and The Second Tuesday
    - Jaro, Benita, The Key, the Lock, the Door in the Wall, (2 folders)
    - Jason, Philip, Biography of Brendan Galvin
    - Jauss, David, Articles of Faith
    - Johnson, B.S., Poems 2
    - Johnson, Larry, Veins
    - Johnson, Larry, Poems
    - Johnson, Mary, Poems
    - Jones, Edward, Island
    - Jones, James, Epigraphs and letter
    - Joyce, William, Poems
    - Joynes, St. Leger M., Under the Coat, Please
    - Kachman, Geneva, Mistress of Fine Arts Initial Examination
    - Kafka, Kimberly, Come Like Shadows
    - Kafka, Kim, Keeping it where the Sun Doesn't Shine
    - Katzenbach, Maria, Short stories
    - Katzenbach, Maria, Naming the Enemy
    - Keeble, John, Yellowfish
    - Kelly, C. Brian, Muskrat Guilt
    - Kempf, Elizabeth, Poems
    - Kempf, Elizabeth, Euphemia
    - Kempowski, Walter, Dog Days, chapters 36-40
    - Kendrick, Stephen, Intro 8 notebook
    - Keyser, Earl, Poems
    - Kibler, James E., Review of My Silk Purse and Yours
    - Kimber, Bob, To Grandmother's House We Go
    - King, Lee, Poems
    - King, Leyland, Song of My Son
    - King, Leyland, Poems
    - Kingbury, Celia, Renaissance Laughter
    - Kline, Christina Baker, Sweet Water (Box WO 17)
    - Kooser, Ted, A Few Attractive Strangers (Box WO 9)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Teaching and the Non-Standard Writer
    - Kreisworth, Martin, Centers, Openings, and Endings: Some Faulknesian Constants
    - Lakehomer, Leona, Poems
    - La Couras, Pete, Short stories
    - Lamont, Nathan Bedford Forrest, Tom Lamarr
    - Lander Paul, Written Away from the Fire
    - Lang, John, Essay on Fred Chappell's Moments of Light
    - Langbaum, Robert, The Revolving Bookstand... and Autobiography and Myth in 'Out of Africa'
    - Lardner, Ted, Bathing in the Rio Grande
    - Larkin, David, The Eternal Family Settles a Question
    - LaRiche, William, Almost Alright?
    - Larson, Clinton, Poems
    - LaSalle, Pete, Dolphin Dreaming
    - LaSalle, Peter, A Guide to Some Small, Border Airports
    - LaSalle, Peter, A Theory of Dentistry and Port-au-Prince
    - Lawrence, Starling, Reunion
    - Layman, Richard, How to Read John Dos Passos' 'Number 1'
    - Leary, D.A., So He Came Down
    - Leon, Poems
    - Leonard, John, Portrait of the First Novelist as a Loser
    - Levkoff, Michael, Notes from Garrett's English 56 class
    - Lewis, J.D., Lying on Bed
    - Lindensmith, Mark, Short-Term Losses (Box WO 10)
    - Lipinsky, Mike, Short story fragment
    - Lish, Gordon, Zimzum
    - Lish, Gordon, A Kind of Magnificence
    - Little, John, Sunday Beer
    - Long, Kate, Prologue to Ordinaries
    - Longley, John Lewis, End of Season
    - Longley, John, Gentle, Into that Good Night, (3 folders)
    - Longley, Judy, My Journey Towards You
    - Longley, Judy, Poems
    - Lopez, Minerva, Essay on In the Labrinthe
    - Lottman, Maryrica, The Dog-Walker
    - Loughran, Joseph, Stand the Champion
    - Low, David, Short story
    - Lowe, Keith, Undercurrents
    - Loyd, Marianne, Poems
    - Lucid, Robert, Anecdotes and Recollections
    - Luschei, Glenna, Mayflower Van Lines
    - Lyll, Jenkins, Like Mango Trees
    - Lyne, Barbara with Mary Wolcott and Katherine Wootus, For Lovers Only
    - Macauley, Robie and Van der Leun, If...
    - Madden, David, Wright Morris' 'In Orbit': An Unbroken Series of Poetic Gestures
    - Magun, Carol, Circling Eden
    - Maiolo, Joeseph, Man of Letters, (2 folders)
    - Maiolo, Joe, Poem
    - Maiolo, Joe, Gloria's Day in the Pasture
    - Maiolo, Joe, Review of The Magic Striptease
    - Mallon, Thomas, Henry and Clara
    - Malm, Ira, Review of Jean Stafford's The Interior Castle
    - Mann, James, Vandal
    - Massey, D.K., The Guard Tower
    - Masters, Hilary, A Stray Shot
    - Masters, Hilary, Death of an Editor
    - Masters, Hilary, What Writer's Block?
    - Masters, Hilary, A Hand for the Python
    - Masters, Hilary, Last Stands, (2 folders)
    - Masters, Hilary, Connections
    - Masters, Hilary, Success, (2 folders)
    - May, Naomi, A Place to Sleep, Reconciliation, A Greek Facade, Exchanges, and Chapter 1 (Box WO 11)
    - Mayo, Michael, Jones and the Old Man
    - Matson, Katinka, Alice, Observation, and Entry
    - Matzke, Mary Frances, Poems
    - Mazzaro, Jerome, Poems
    - McAuley, James J., Cullen's Loss
    - McAuley, James, Poems
    - McAuley, James, After the Blizzard
    - McBuilkin, Frank, Rufus Brillingham: Tragedy of the Farm
    - McCall, Herbert, Untitled story
    - McCloskey, Mark, Poems
    - McCollins, William, Poems
    - McCorkle, Jill, July 7: A Novel, (2 folders)
    - McCullough, F.W., The Music
    - McCullough, Frank, The Night They Got Agnew
    - McDougall, Jo, The Woman in the Next Booth
    - McFee, Michael, Prospectus
    - McGlassom, Nancy, Untitled story
    - McGonigle, Tom, Reviews
    - McGonigle, Tom, Poems
    - McGonigle, Thomas, The Corpse Dream of N. Petkov
    - McGonigle, Thomas, The Pastures of Stupidity and The Testimonial Dinner
    - McGovern, P.A., Going Home
    - McHaney, Tom, The Shoplifter
    - McHaney, Tom, The Death of the Fox
    - McHaney, Tom, 'Sanctuary' and Frazer's Slain Kings
    - McMillen, Excerpt from book
    - McQuilkin, Frank, Poems
    - Meriwether, James, What Happens When You Eat Magnolias?
    - Meriwether, James, Dashes in Hemingway's 'A Farewell to Arms'
    - Meriwether, James, Notes on Textual History of 'The Sound and the Fury'
    - Meriwether, James, Prefatory Note by Faulkner for Compson Appendix
    - Mewshaw, Mike, Waking Slow
    - Mewshaw, Mike, Untitled, (2 folders)
    - Miles, Elizabeth, Poems
    - Miles, Jack, Economics and Politics of Book Reviewing
    - Miller, Vassar, Poems
    - Miller, Vassar, Pact
    - Miller, Vassar, False Spring
    - Milligan, Thomas, Poems and an autobiographical sketch
    - Millman, Larry, King of Beasts
    - Millman, Larry, Neanderthals
    - Millman, Lawrence, The Book of Origins
    - Millman, Lawrence, The Ballad of Hero Jesse, (2 folders)
    - Millman, Lawrence, Short stories
    - Millman, Lawrence, Moon/Snail/Sonata
    - Millman, Lawrence, Smell of Earth and Clay: Greenlandic Charms, Spells, and Songs
    - Mills, Wil, Poems
    - Millstein, Stuart, Two for Tea, Bubble Bath, From House to House, and other poems
    - Moffett, Judy, Poems, (2 folders) (Box WO 12)
    - Montgomery, Marion, The Country, Here
    - Moore, Elizabeth, Pearls and Ash, (2 folders)
    - Moore, Harold, The Perfect Hi-Fi and The Incident at Billy Springs
    - Moore, J.R., Some Night Thoughts on Beckett
    - Moore, Richard, Poems
    - Moore, Richard, A Question of Survival, (2 folders)
    - Moore, Richard, The No Self, the Little Self, and the Poets
    - Morris, John S., And the Sun
    - Morris, Robert, The Poet Comes Home
    - Morrison, Markesan, The Knee-Kisser
    - Moorman, David, Scale: A Preview
    - Moxley, Joseph, Creative Writing in America
    - Mueller, Craig, Marlowe, then Shakespeare, then Jonson
    - Mulholland, Paige E., So You Want to Achieve Excellence
    - Musing, Sandra, George Garrett: A Bibliography
    - Myers, Lucas, The Feral Girl
    - Myers, Lucas, Two plays
    - Myers, Lucas, Poems
    - Myers, Lucas, Ah, Youth...
    - Napoli, Donna Jo, Stories
    - Nassar, Eugene, Both God and Fake
    - Nesbitt, Paula, Sky Child
    - Nicholson, Jacques, Justin Revisited
    - Nims, John Frederick, Zany in Denim
    - Noertker, Joseph, Transit of Jordan
    - O'Connell, Richard, Translation of Irish monastic poems
    - O'Connor, Sarah, Exiled: A Memoir
    - O'Connor, Tom, Edmund Campion, S.J.
    - Orlee, Jacqueline, Juliet of the Spirits
    - Palmer, Bryan, Somewhere Through the Wilderness
    - Palmer, Bryan, The Only Way
    - Parker, Michael, Hello Down There, (2 folders)
    - Parks, Brad, Getting People Hurt
    - Parks, Sarah, In Orbit
    - Patrick, W.B., Poems
    - Pawlowski, Robert, The Poetry of Wallace Stevens and Myth as Metaphor
    - Peck, John, Letting Up
    - Peden, William, Queenie's Pups, Date Palms and Coliseum, and Absent Thee from Felicity
    - Peden, William, review of Garrett's Maggots in the Basement and The Blue Slipper
    - Peden, William, The Cross-Country Dog
    - Peden, William, Fragments from the Workbook of an Obscure Writer
    - Peet, James M., Modern Light on the Soul
    - Peet, Mel, Dwight MacDonald or Politics, (5 folders)
    - Penick, Douglas, Chinese Nights
    - Penick, D.J., The Conquest of Mexico
    - Perkins, D.A., The Ancient Book of Ancient Time
    - Perry, Laurie Lynn, A Collection of Poems
    - Peter, Emmett, review of Poison Pen
    - Petracca, Joseph, The Proud Rebel
    - Pfeil, Fred, MLA and Poker Fugue (Box WO 13)
    - Pickerel, Paul, Prints of critical literary essays
    - Pierson, Amanda, Dancing on Water
    - Pierson, Mandy, Relative Terms, Consolation, and other stories
    - Ponder, Dulane, Poems
    - Ponder, Leanne, Poems
    - Poster, Carol, Poems, (5 folders)
    - Poster, Carol, Bag Ladies Never Beg
    - Poster, Carol, Voyages
    - Poster, Carol, A Game
    - Poster, Carol, Worms and Water
    - Poster, Carol, Intro to Poetry
    - Poster, Carol, Deceiving the Worms
    - Poster, Carol, The Purity of Diction in O.B. Hardison's Verse
    - Poster, Carol, Blackbird
    - Poster, Carol, Surrounded by Dangerous Things
    - Poster, Carol, Poems of Jacques Prevert, (2 folders)
    - Price, Reynolds, A Long and Happy Life
    - Preston, D.S., Narrow Passage and Chatham
    - Prunty, Wyatt, The Distance into Place
    - Prunty, Wyatt, Allegory to Causality: Robert Lowell's Poetic Shift
    - Pryse, Marjorie, Proposal and request for fellowship
    - Purviance, Donald, Little Seizures, (2 folders)
    - Purviance, Donald, Dead Giveaway
    - Quigley, Peter, Roasted Chestnuts at Christmas
    - Ramsey, Paul, The Naming of Adam
    - Randall, Nora, Poems
    - Rath, Roger, The Model and Trailers
    - Raun, Timothy, Anger Unfinished
    - Ray, David, You Can't Go Home Again, You Sonofabitch!
    - Ray, David, Poems
    - Real, Jere, VQR is Varied
    - Reddick, Tom, Excerpts from Whose Bright Stars?
    - Reed, Kit, Outline for revision
    - Reed, Kit, Florida on my Mind
    - Reed, Kit, Oblivion is a ...
    - Rees, Ennis, Poems ( folder)
    - Rees, Ennis, In the Dallas Airport
    - Reist, John, Poetry of Permanent Things
    - Reiter, Thomas, Poems
    - Reiter, Thomas, At a Nephew's Grave and A Moment of Geese
    - Rigsbee, David, Ratio: poems
    - Robinson, Phil Alden, Field of Dreams
    - Robinson, William, Description of an anthology of essays on movies
    - Rodenbeck, Jon von B., The Voyeurs
    - Roemer, Jackie, Sweet
    - Rollyson, Carl, Rebecca West at 100: A Saga of the Century
    - Rooney, Andrew, Paradise Person and Walter Stukowski: Reg'lar Guy
    - Roper, John, Foreword to bio of Howard Kester and a report on the series of bios
    - Rosen, Ken, Mountains, etc.
    - Rosen, Kenneth, The Giant Day
    - Ross, Jean W., Biography of John Cheever
    - Rubin, Louis, The Literary Attacks on Styron's 'Nat Turner'
    - Rubin, Louis, Notes on a Rear-Guard Action
    - Rubin, Louis, Grant proposals
    - Ruffin, Paul, The Mosquito
    - Ruffin, Paul, The Man Who Would Be God (Box WO 14)
    - Ruffin, Paul, Book Reviewing in Texas
    - Ruffin, Paul, Our Women
    - Ruffin, Paul, The Mosquito
    - Russell, Peter, Miscellaneous writings
    - Ryan, Richard, To Aesop
    - Sage, Norman, Seven Blackberries
    - St. Clair, Jeffrey, Poems
    - Sanders, Scott Russell, Review of The Succession for Chicago Sun Times
    - Sanders, Scott, Book Week review of The Succession
    - Sanders, Scott, The First Journey of Jason Moss
    - Sandy, Stephen, Poems, (3 folders)
    - Sandy, Stephen, Essay on Theodore Holmes
    - Sandy, Stephen, Flight of Steps
    - Sandy, Stephen, Experienced Bards
    - Saunders, Budd, They Ain't Got No Respect
    - Sawicki, Phillip, It's Art
    - Schabert, Ina, Report, (2 folders)
    - Scherman, Peter, Cliffs of Clay
    - Scholes, Robert, Afterword on Vonnegut
    - Schuster, Alberta, So What Did You Learn at School Today?
    - Scott, Carolyne, Good-bye, Hello Joe
    - Scott, Nathan, The Poetry of Richard Wilbur
    - Scott, Nathan, Poetry and Prayer
    - Scott, Nathan A., Jr., The New 'Trahison des Clercs'
    - Sears, Patricia, The Girl in the Black Raincoat
    - Seay, James, Does Anyone wanna Buy My Little Brother?
    - Seferis, George, Poems
    - Seligmann, Nancy, Thought-Sex
    - Seshachari, Neila C., 'F' is for Fugitive
    - Settle, Mary Lee, Cage of Bone (Box WO 17)
    - Settle, Mary Lee, An Inquiry into the Teaching of Writing as an Art (Box WO 14)
    - Settle, Mary Lee, Review of Henry Carlisle's Voyage to the 1st of Dec.
    - Settle, Mary Lee, Paragraph 11
    - Settle, Mary Lee, The Days of October
    - Seward, William, F. Scott Fitzgerald's Associations...
    - Sharp, Rhod, Solo
    - Shawn, Richard, The Sleeper
    - Shaya, Greg, Travels in Nihilon
    - Sheldon, Tim, Poems
    - Simmons, Edgar, Poems
    - Simmons, J. Edgar, Motivation: the Moral Eroticism and The Green Key
    - Simms, L.L., Poems
    - Simon, Rose, Poems
    - Singer, Ron, Spots
    - Slavitt, David, Da Ponte
    - Slavitt, David, Sorrows of Fat City: Bloom and the Decline of Civility
    - Slavitt, David, Translations of hymns of Prudentius
    - Slavitt, David, Poems
    - Slavitt, David, Luke's Book
    - Slavitt, David, Translation of Seneca's Medea
    - Slavitt, David, The Cliff
    - Slavitt, David, The Year in the Short Story, 1986-1994, (5 folders)
    - Slavitt, David, Translation of The Fables of Avianus
    - Slavitt, David, Translation of Duessa
    - Slavitt, David, Translations of epigrams of John Owens
    - Slavitt, David, Dreams, Ideals, and Jokes
    - Slavitt, David, Translation of Ovid's Ibis
    - Slavitt, David, Rounding the Horn and other poems
    - Slavitt, David, History, Fate, and Freedom: A Look at George Garrett's New Novel
    - Slavitt, David, King Saul
    - Slavitt, David, Collected Poems
    - Slavitt, David, Basic Training
    - Slavitt, David, Short Stories Are Not Real Life, (2 folders)
    - Slavitt, David, Publish and Perish
    - Slavitt, David, Coming Out Every Week
    - Slavitt, David, Get Thee to a Nunnery: Two Shakespearean Metafictions
    - Slavitt, David, Translation of Thyestes
    - Slavitt, David, Duessa's Version
    - Slavitt, David, 'The Succession': George Garrett's Book for All Seasons
    - Slavitt, David, Name Six Famous Belgians
    - Slavitt, David, Ovid in Exile
    - Slavitt, David, Review of Richard Burgin's Man Without Memory and David Huddle's The High Spirits
    - Sloan, James Park, A Small War
    - Smith, Keith, Life Sentences (Box WO 15)
    - Smith, R.B., Stay Close to Your Desks and Never Go to Sea
    - Smith, William Jay, Poems
    - Snow, Wilbert, Poems
    - Soderfelt, Eloise, Poems
    - Sokolov, Raymond, Who Should Pay the Piper for Piss Christ?
    - Solomon, Andy, Review of The Writer's Chapbook
    - Sonde, Susan, The Saved
    - Sopko, John, The Robbery and Beyond the High Grass
    - Sorrells, Robert, The Blacktop Champion of Ickey Honey and other stories
    - Spears, Monroe K. and Wier, Allen, Reviews of Entered from the Sun, (2 folders)
    - Spelvin, George, Fragments from the Notebooks...
    - Spyker, John H., A One Night Stand-In
    - Standiford, Les, Miscellaneous papers
    - Standiford, Les, Deal, (2 folders)
    - Stanford, Frank, Poems, (2 folders)
    - Stanton, Maura, Nijinsky, John McCormack, and Cries of Swimmers
    - Steinke, Darcey, My Father's Girlfriends and On This Bare Island
    - Steinke, Darcey, Obedience
    - Steinke, Jonathan Paul, Un Sejour dans la Nuit
    - Stern, Horst, The Last Hunt
    - Stevens, Mariflo, Some Say Tomato
    - Stevenson, John, Reflections from a Retired Position
    - Still, Mary, Chapters 1 & 2 from an unfinished novel
    - Stillwell, Sgt. Harry E., World on Fire
    - Stokesbury, Leon, Often in Different Landscapes
    - Sullivan, Chester, The Mountain Quail
    - Sullivan, Walter, Afterwords
    - Sullivan, Walter, Fiction in a Dry Season: Some Signs of Hope
    - Sullivan, Walter, The Recovery of Literature
    - Taylor, F.H. Griffin, A Point in Time, A Place in Space
    - Taylor, Henry, A Road Sufficient for the Purpose
    - Taylor, Henry, Good-bye to the Goya Girl
    - Taylor, Henry, After a Movie and How to Enjoy a Film Festival
    - Taylor, Peter, Their Losses and Two Pilgrims
    - Teto, Randeane, Merle's and Marilyn's Mink Ranch
    - Theroux, Alexander, Poems
    - Theroux, Alexander, Christmas Eve at the Gordon Crumms
    - Theroux, Alexander, The Confessions of Mrs. Motherwell
    - Thompson, Bill, The Journey of the Fisher King, (2 folders)
    - Thompson, Bill, Excerpt from Journey of the Fisher King
    - Thompson, Burn, Poems
    - Threthewey, Eric, Evening Knowledge
    - Tillinghast, Richard, Our Flag Was Still There, (2 folders)
    - Tillinghast, Richard, 15 poems by Richard Tillinghast
    - Tilghman, Christopher, The Long Way Around
    - Topp, Bob, The Horns of the Ram
    - Torstenson, Ann, Poems
    - Trainer, Mark, Biography of Peter Taylor
    - Trotti, Lamar, The Ox-Bow Incident (Box WO 16)
    - Truesdale, C.W., Moon Shots
    - Turneau, Ted, Poems
    - Tuttleton, James W., The Tension Between Emerson and Hawthorne
    - Vance, Jane Gentry, Review of Garrett's Understanding Mary Lee Settle
    - Vella, Augusta Evalee, Son
    - Waldan, Roy, Story
    - Walker, David, Poems
    - Walker, David, Moving Out: poems 1962-69
    - Wall, Eamonn, Review of Tom McGonigle's Going to Patchoque
    - Wallace, Connie, Hillary Highheels
    - Walters, Neal Lawrence, In Barefoot Country
    - Walton, Jackie, Budapest Series, Part 1
    - Walton, Jackie, The Pretense of Air, (2 folders)
    - Walton, Jackie, The Third Floor
    - Walton, Jackie, Untitled
    - Walton, Jacqueline, Blood from a Stone
    - Walton, Kathy, Daddy
    - Warner, William, Poems
    - Warren, Barbara, Who Kissed the Corpse?, (2 folders)
    - Weiseman, Jack, Poems
    - Weismiller, E.R., Poems
    - Weissberg, Melissa, Flight Patterns
    - Weissberg, Melissa, No Haven
    - West, Woody, A Graduation Address for '92.
    - Whalen, Tom, The Ride
    - Whalen, Tom, Chozen at 4 am
    - Whalen, Tom, My Only Homerun
    - Whalen, Tom, Film Noir: Killer Style
    - Whalen, Tom, Professors
    - Whalen, Tom, The Reader becomes Text Methods of Experimentation in Garrett's 'Elizabeth and James'
    - Whalen, Tom, Head in a Box
    - White, Lourine, Echo From a Sheltered Valley
    - Whitehall, John, Review of Louis Rubin's An Apple for My Teacher
    - Wier, Allen, Writing as an Act of Faith
    - Wier, Allen, Ghosts Made Flesh, review of Garrett's Entered From the Sun
    - Wilbur, Ellen, Short stories
    - Wilbur, Ellen, Winds and Birds and Human Voices, (2 folders)
    - Wilbur, Ellen, At the V.A. Hospital
    - Wilbur, Ellen, The History Teacher
    - Wilken, Robert, The Christian Intellectual Tradition
    - Williams, Miller, Poems
    - Willingham, Calder, How to Write Novels and Screenplays
    - Wilson, Clyde, Should the South Survive?
    - Wilson, Clyde, Review of Garrett's Understanding Mary Lee Settle
    - Wingate, Jane, Going on the Roof
    - Winehap, Bob, Juan
    - Wise, Hope, A Rich Widow
    - Wise, Hope, Annie's Story and poems
    - Wister, Fanny Kemble, Owen Wister' Out West: His Journals and Letters
    - Woelfel, Sal, The Duckling Essays
    - Woiwode, Larry, Television: the Cyclops that Eats Books
    - Wolfe, Gregory, Novels as History: the Art of Andrew Lytle
    - Wood, George R., Notes on Attempted Sanity
    - Wright, Stephen, Of Death, No News
    - Wright, Stuart, George Garrett: A Bibliographic Chronicle
    - Yates, James, Confusions on Entrances to a Bird House
    - Yates, James, Innocent Bystanders
    - Yount, John, Toots in Solitude, (2 folders)
    - Yount, John, Hardcastle, (2 folders)
- Correspondence Series, 1929-1995 and undated
  The correspondence series is divided into five subseries: the Chronological Correspondence Subseries, and Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries A, B, C, and D.
  - Chronological Correspondence Subseries, 1929-1995 and undated (bulk 1940-1995)
    Contains letters from students, colleagues, friends, literary figures, and family members concerning literary, academic, and personal matters. Arranged chronologically by year. Box 1 contains material pertaining to Garrett's childhood and early education and is arranged in a separate run in chronological order.
    - 1929-1941, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 1)
    - 1941-1943, (2 folders)
    - 1941-1943, (2 folders)
    - 1941-1944, (3 folders)
    - 1942-1946: Sewanee Military Academy, (2 folders)
    - 1946-1947: Princeton Correspondence, (1 folder)
    - 1947: Camp Mt. Mitchell, (1 folder)
    - 1947: The Hill School, (2 folders)
    - 1940-1952: Personal, (2 folders)
    - 1940, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1941, (1 folder)
    - 1945, (1 folder)
    - 1947, (1 folder)
    - 1948, (1 folder)
    - 1949, (1 folder)
    - 1950, (1 folder)
    - 1951, (1 folder)
    - 1955, (1 folder)
    - 1957, (1 folder)
    - 1958, (1 folder)
    - 1959, (1 folder)
    - 1960, (1 folder)
    - 1961, (1 folder)
    - 1961 Oct. 11-1964 Dec. 4, (1 folder)
    - 1962, (1 folder)
    - 1963, (1 folder)
    - 1964, (1 folder)
    - 1965, (1 folder)
    - 1965 Jan. 10-1968 Jun. 16, (1 folder)
    - 1966, (1 folder)
    - 1967, (2 folders)
    - 1968, (4 folders)
    - 1969, (2 folders)
    - 1970, (1-3 of 11 folders)
    - 1970, (4-11 of 11 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 3)
    - 1971, (3 folders)
    - 1972, (3 folders)
    - 1973, (2 folders)
    - 1974, (2 folders)
    - 1975, (2 folders)
    - 1976, (1 folder)
    - 1977, (2 folders)
    - 1978, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 4)
    - 1979, (2 folders)
    - 1980, (2 folders)
    - 1981, (3 folders)
    - 1982, (4 folders)
    - 1983, (12 folders)
    - 1984 (1-2 of 17 folders)
    - 1984 (3-17 of 17 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 5)
    - 1985 (1-7 of 11 folders)
    - 1985 (8-11 of 11 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 6)
    - 1986, (10 folders)
    - 1987 (1-5 of 17 folders)
    - 1987 (6-17 of 17 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 7)
    - 1988 (1-5 of 28 folders)
    - 1988 (6-22 of 28 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 8)
    - 1988 (23-28 of 28 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 9)
    - 1989 (1-12 of 27 folders)
    - 1989 (13-27 of 27 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 10)
    - 1990 (1-19 of 29 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 11)
    - 1990 (20-29 of 29 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 12)
    - 1991 (1-7 of 23 folders)
    - 1991 (8-19 of 23 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 13)
    - 1991 (20-23 of 23 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 14)
    - 1992 (1-12 of 24 folders)
    - 1992 (13-24 of 24 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 15)
    - 1993 (1-4 of 20 folders)
    - 1993 (5-20 of 20 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 16)
    - 1994 (1-12 of 14 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 17)
    - 1994 (13-14 of 14 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 18)
    - 1995, (6 folders)
    - N.d., (21 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 19)
    - N.d., (15 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 20)
  - Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries: Group A, ca. 1961-1995 and undated